http://www.halloweenexpress.com/privacy-policy/

30% Off
HOLIDAY DEALS. No Minimum. Click for Details
Largest Selection on the PlanetSame Day Shipping
Search
Exact Match Search?
Search
Exact Match Search?
Flapper Accessories
Footwear - Misc.
Evil Court
Fairy-Licious!
Privacy Policy
We take your business seriously and use every reasonable precaution necessary to ensure your shopping experience is safe! We want you to be aware of what kind of information we obtain from you, how we use this information, and how you can control its use. By using this site, you consent to this Privacy Policy.
We operate this web site under the name of HalloweenExpress.com owned and operated by ASADART LLC, dba ASADART E-Commerce Specialty Shops, a Kentucky Limited Liability Corporation. As such, when you provide information to us, this information may be combined or shared between current or future entities and subsidiaries.
What personally identifiable information is collected?In order to provide you superior service, communicate marketing promotions which we believe will be of interest to you, and to administer our business,we may gather the following personal information (except where prohibited by law): salutation, name (first/middle/last), billing and shipping addresses, company name (if applicable), email address, phone/fax number (if applicable), payment type, credit card type/number/expiration date. How this information is used and how we protect information collected from online purchases is explained below.
How is the collected information used?We use your personally identifiable information to provide superior service in the following areas: to process, fulfill and track online orders; bill your credit card for purchases; respond to your customer service inquiries or requests; provide requested services such as Coupon and Gift Voucher redemption and return/exchange information; offer information regarding products and services based on your interests or past purchases; hold contests, giveaways, drawings and promotions; administer shopping or reward club accounts; conduct and administer surveys; mail marketing/sales material via email or postal mail; set up commercial accounts; sign up for new credit card promotions; or use it for other general business purposes to further enhance our business relationship with you.
To enhance your online experience with us, we may also collect aggregate information as to which pages you visit, search terms used, etc. - in order to measure the effectiveness of our website and identify areas for improvement (product selection, site performance and/or to streamline the purchasing processes).
How do we use cookies and technology in our website?HalloweenExpress.com sets a cookie on your computer to record certain information during your online visit (session). No personally identifiable information is stored within this cookie. The benefit to you is the ability to save items added to your shopping bag and store them on our server for future reference. These cookies do not gather sensitive information like your name, address, credit card number, etc., if you do not specifically give that information to us voluntarily. If you have given us that information, cookies enable us to recall it (and save you the trouble of entering it all over again) each time you visit our site.
Our web server collects the addresses of the web sites that visitors came from before visiting our site, which browser was used to view our site and search terms entered on our site. Without making use of any personally identifiable information, we may track the pages visited to help us understand how customers use our site. This helps us make decisions on how to create a better experience for you in the future.
At your option, if you delete our cookies, you will limit our ability to personalize the site for your next visit. However, deleting a cookie will not prevent you from visiting our site and making purchases.
Who are the third party entities with whom we may share your personally identifiable information? We may use third party companies in limited ways. We may provide your information to reputable organizations that help us to fulfill services to you on our behalf. For example, we use may use companies to authorize credit card transactions, to ship packages,, etc. We may provide information to others to help us maintain records and analyze sales data. We use customer information providers to augment and improve the accuracy of our customer database. We hire third parties to distribute postal and email communications with our offers or important information on our behalf. The third party companies we hire are not authorized to use your information for any reason other than to provide the above stated services for which we contract them to perform.
Opt-Out / Unsubscribe Every promotional email we send includes an OPT-OUT link at the bottom of the email. As an option, you can also use THIS LINK TO OPT-OUT of all future Halloween Express promotional emails.
×
Want Discounts?
Need Help?
Contact Us
Need Help?
Contact Us
Retail Vendors
Contact Us
